(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-04T01:09:54.824996",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
堕天使
[Title: Fallen Angel]
悩める人の子よ
O child of man, lost in worry,
人ならざる者よ
O non-human being,
合間絶えず目指す天よ
O heaven aimed for without fail,
生きていけ私
Live on, my self.
目を逸らした過去も
The past I looked away from,
退屈な未来も
and the boring future too—
カウンセリング やれやれ
counseling, good grief.
古今東西 ピースピース
Peace, peace, through all times and places!
ねねねね 何だかどうして 戦っているようなそんな気がするの
Hey, hey, hey, hey, why do I feel like I'm fighting somehow?
過去の自分自分自分と思う
I keep thinking, "My past self, my past self, my past self."
とっくに死んでる透明な亡霊と対決
A duel with a transparent ghost long dead,
一対一で言った一言の奥の奥
deep within that single word spoken one-on-one.
残念 もう居ないのに あれ そっちが良い愛らしさに
Too bad, even though it's gone now... Huh? To that lovely charm over there,
透かされているのは今の自分
it's my present self that's being see-through.
ナンセンス 消えないレッテル
Nonsense, an indelible label,
家柄コンプレックス
family background complex,
取り憑かれているみたい
like I'm possessed,
泣きついたまま まだ 離れられない 在りし日の自分
clinging onto and still unable to let go of my former self.
信じ合えない Oh my, Oh my way
We can't believe in each other, oh my, oh my way.
さあ 生きていることとは変わり続けることで
Now, to be alive means to keep changing,
不況に甘んじて満足するなよ
So don't settle for unhappiness and be satisfied!
幸せになろうとしないなんて滑稽だろ
It's ridiculous not even trying to be happy, right?
幾回 幾回 ファンタジー 続きは折れるか 跳ね返るか
How many cycles of fantasy? Will the continuation bend or bounce back?
出会って追ってやっと始まるストーリー
Meeting, chasing, and finally the story begins.
さあ一握だけの命か 儚き Lie PEACE PEACE
Is it a life of just a handful? A fleeting lie, peace peace!
Past, future, can't change the past
Past, future, what about the future?
何がどうして未来になんとなくの
Why is it that regarding the future,
希望なんて抱けないような気がしても
I feel like I can't even hold any vague hope?
随分生きてる既視感とテンプレで食傷
Having lived so long, fed up with deja vu and cliches,
素敵な出来事の気配もない
There's not even a sign of wonderful events happening.
積んだ経験の因果経過が活かされた神話と退屈な進化
A myth where accrued experience yields results, and a boring evolution.
要は刺激が欲しいんだ 飽きちゃった 慣れちゃった
Simply put, I want excitement, I'm bored of it, used to it.
なんて整っていくガイドライン
Look at those neat guidelines being set,
増えるコンプライアンス
Increasing compliance,
塞がれていく選択肢
Options being blocked off,
いつからか
Since when?
でもどれもこれも同じ味がする
Yet all of them taste exactly the same.
信じ合えない Oh my, Oh my way
We can't believe in each other, oh my, oh my way.
さあ いつも言う過去も未来も今に宿んだ
Now, the past and future I always talk about dwell in the present.
生きていることを愚直に果たせよ
Fulfill the act of living honestly!
目指せハッピーエンド
Aim for a happy ending!
信じ合えない お前に言ってるんだ
I'm talking to you, who can't believe in others!
幸せを諦めてしまうなんて人かい？
Are you really someone who just gives up on happiness?
ただ苦しみに慣れて耐えているだけじゃ
Just getting used to suffering and enduring it,
死んでるも同然 しかばねのUNDEAD
Is no different from being dead, a corpse of UNDEAD!
大盤振舞せよ 生きているんだろう？
Go all out! You're alive, aren't you?
不幸に浸るのも
Whether wallowing in misfortune,
幸せになるのも
Or becoming happy,
そう全部全部お前だ
Yes, it's all, all up to you!
古今東西一切合切 最新版 Showcases PEACE PEACE
All times and places, everything altogether, latest showcases, peace peace!
Past, future, can't change the past
Past, future, what about the future?
人なるトコロ 煮詰まれいごと生き抜くの
Where humans gather, push through every dilemma,
だけどモノばかり モノガタリ
Yet it's all just things, a story.
花になって
[Title: Becoming a Flower]
陰にそっと隠れようが良いんじゃない？
Wouldn't it be fine to quietly hide in the shadows?
蕾のような花だってあるんじゃない？
Aren't there flowers that stay like buds, too?
秘密にして守るのが良いんじゃない？
Wouldn't it be fine to keep it a secret and protect it?
誰にも邪魔されず 華麗に咲いている
Blooming gorgeously, undisturbed by anyone.
甘い苦いにハマらない
Not getting trapped in sweet or bitter,
その判断がくだらない
That kind of judgment is foolish.
気に病んで下を向かないでいて
Don't worry and look down.
愛に慣れちゃえない
Unable to get used to love,
無駄に飾らない
Not decorating unnecessarily.
綺麗にされた花瓶も
Neither a prettied-up vase,
肥やしも何もいらない
Nor fertilizer, nor anything is needed.
その姿が美しい
Just as you are, you're beautiful.
花になって
Become a flower,
ほらニヒルに笑って
Look, smile nihilistically.
その顔にぞくぞくして目が離せない
Thrilled by that face, I can't take my eyes off you.
味見して
Taste it,
君の毒は私の薬って
Saying, "Your poison is my medicine,"
包んであげるから
Because I'll wrap it up for you,
笑って
Smile.
ねぇ 会いたい 会いたい
Hey, I want to see you, I want to see you.
その笑顔に会いたい 会いたい
I want to see that smile, I want to see it.
って言えば笑ってくれるかな
If I say that, will you smile for me?
陰から支えるくらいはいいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine at least to support from the shadows?
欲を言えばこの手で咲かせてみせたい
If I'm being greedy, I want to make you bloom with my own hands.
病のように
Like a disease,
心を
My heart...
狂わせ
...driven mad,
枯らしたくないのさ
I don't want to let it wither.
光が届かずとも
Even if the light doesn't reach,
水をあげ続けようから
Shall I keep watering you?
いい加減に気づいて
Realize it already,
君は素敵だって
That you are wonderful!
自惚れてもっとお大事に
Be full of yourself and take better care of yourself.
無自覚なまま
Unconsciously,
愛を蓄えて
Store up love.
綺麗にされた花瓶も
Neither a prettied-up vase,
肥やしも何もいらない
Nor fertilizer, nor anything is needed.
その姿で咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly in that very form!
花になって
Become a flower,
ほらニヒルに笑って
Look, smile nihilistically.
その顔にぞくぞくして目が離せない
Thrilled by that face, I can't take my eyes off you.
味見して
Taste it.
ねえ
Hey,
君の毒は私の薬って
"Your poison is my medicine," you said,
包んだから
so since I embraced it...
楽にして
ease your mind.
君の闇は私の光って
"Your darkness is my light," you said,
愛したから
so since I loved it...
笑って
smile for me.
はーい！皆さんこんかなた〜！
Hi! Everyone, kon-kanata~!
キャッチコピーは握力50キロ！ギュッギュッ！握りつぶしちゃうぞ！ホロライブ4期生、天音かなたです！
My catchphrase is 50kg grip strength! Squeeze squeeze! I'll crush you! I'm Hololive 4th Gen, Amane Kanata!
ということでね、2曲お聴きいただきましたがね、
So then, you've listened to two songs so far!
今回も生誕ライブ始まってまいりました！
My birthday live stream has officially begun!
皆さんぜひね、ハッシュタグを使っていっぱいね、つぶやいてください！ポストしてください！
Everyone, please post lots of tweets using the hashtag! Please post!
ハッシュタグはね、#天音かなた生誕祭 でございます！
The hashtag is #天音かなた生誕祭!
すごいシンプルでしょう？
Super simple, right?
ぜひね、色々つぶやいてもらえたら嬉しいなと思います！そしてこのステージ見てください！
I'd be really happy if you tweet all your thoughts! And look at this stage!
うわぁ、すごーい！これすごいでしょ、めちゃめちゃ綺麗でしょ！
Woah, incredible! Isn't this awesome? It's so pretty!
いや、なぜかと言いますとですね、
Well, as for why...
今回の生誕も実はちょっとストーリーがありまして、皆さんに何度も見て考えてもらいたいなと思うんですが、
This birthday live actually has a bit of a story behind it, which I hope you'll watch over and over and think about...
天使と堕天使が...ま、ちょっとね、堕天使の方が世界を滅ぼしたいらしくて、
An angel and a fallen angel... well, the fallen angel apparently wants to destroy the world,
で、天使が立ちはだかって、行って、みたいな...
and the angel stands in her way, and so on...
で、天使が守る...みたいな、世界を守るで「いや、やるぜ」みたいな、テーマは「戦い」な感じになっておりますので、
So the angel protects... protecting the world like, "Alright, let's do this!" The theme is "battle"...
ぜひそのあたりも意識して、歌でバトル、見てくれたら嬉しいなと思います！
So please keep that in mind and enjoy watching our battle through song!
ふぅ〜言いのこしたことはないかな？
Phew~ Did I leave anything unsaid?
またね、歌っていきますのでよろしくお願いします！お！
I'm going to keep singing, so please stay tuned! Oh?
なんか...空が泣きそうじゃない？あ...
Somehow... doesn't the sky look like it's about to cry? Ah...
それでは皆さん、引き続きライブをお楽しみください！
Alright everyone, please continue to enjoy the live stream!
夢が覚めた 酔いどれ知らず
Waking from a dream, unaware of drunkenness
争いごとは 夜が明けるまで
Conflicts last until the night breaks
くたびれては 酷く見える
Exhausted, looking terrible
一千の声は 声が枯れるまで
A thousand voices, until their voices go hoarse
うっちゃる幸せ ずっと醒めないで
Throwing away happiness, never wake up
あなたの声に 耳を貸すときまで
Until the moment I lend an ear to your voice
屈する態度で 言葉さえなくて
With a submissive attitude, without even words
体を染めて
Staining my body...
そして
And then...
泥々 はられあられ ホウライ そう 悪くないわ
Muddy, pelted with hail, Penglai... yes, it's not so bad
屈する 先まで ミリグラム
Yielding down to the last milligram
酩酊 重ね重ね 存外 そう 悪くないわ
Drunkenness, over and over, surprisingly... yes, it's not so bad
酔いどれ知らずの恋敵 だから
Because we're love rivals who know no drunkenness
ウタの声は 数知らず
Countless singing voices
迷い込んだら そこは君の××
If you wander in, that's your XX
ねぇ見てきれい 白昼夢ロンド
Hey, look how pretty, a daydream rondo
一千を隠して 十を吐くだけ
Hiding a thousand, just spitting out ten
一家の幸せ きっと晴れないで
A family's happiness, surely never clearing up
あなたのそばに 耳を貸すときまで
Until the moment I lend an ear by your side
屈する態度で 言葉さえなくて
With a submissive attitude, without even words
心を染めて
Staining my heart...
それは
That is...
泥々 はられあられ 将来像 悪くないわ
Muddy, pelted with hail, a future vision that's not so bad
屈する 私は 生きている
Yielding, I am alive
酩酊 重ね重ね 存外 そう 悪くないわ
Drunkenness, over and over, surprisingly... yes, it's not so bad
酔いどれ知らずの物語
The story of one unaware of drunkenness
深く底に突き刺さらない言葉で誰かを傷つけた
I hurt someone with shallow words that didn't penetrate deep inside
なにやってもうまくいかない 脳内じゃ戦争だもんね 突っ立ってたって
Nothing I do goes right, it's a war in my brain anyway, even if I'm standing still
なにやってもうまくいかない 愛して 愛して
Nothing I do goes right, love me, love me
なにやってもうまくいかない 第三次世界大戦の聞いたことあんだ
Nothing I do goes right, I've heard of World War III
なにやってもうまくいかない なにやってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right, nothing I do goes right
ほーら見てすごいでしょうが 発端に何？スパイや魔女が飛び交うフィールド
Look, isn't it amazing? What's at the root? A field where spies and witches fly about
淡々と
Indifferently,
オリジナリティとか
originality and stuff,
なんだか模索していけって
telling me to search for something like that.
イバラでバラバラなの？ ないです
In tatters from thorns? No way.
軟膏塗っときゃ分かんない お邪魔虫が
Put on some ointment and no one knows, the pests
まだ評価されてんだ 正常化してるよ
are still being evaluated, "I'm back to normal,"
なぁって そっちの台詞のような
like you're one to talk.
まぁいいから全部聞き流してください どうか
Well whatever, please just ignore it all, okay?
ポイ捨てゴミくず 汚い言葉で誰かを傷つけた
Trash thrown away, hurting someone with filthy words...
何をやってもうまくいかない 脳内大戦争だもんね 突っ立ってたって
Nothing I do goes right, there's a total war in my brain even while standing around.
愛して 愛して
Love me, love me.
第三者目線は手厚い手当
A third party's perspective offers generous care.
何をやってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right.
段々とさ 気付いてんだ どうかしてたって
Gradually I'm realizing that I was out of my mind,
どうして？ どうして？
Why? Why?
重客は満杯だもんね じっと過ごしてたって
The place is packed with guests, even if I just stay still.
何をやってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right.
そうか 傷ついて傷ついて
I see, getting hurt and hurt,
あっという間に シチュエーションは振ってんです
In an instant, the situation swings completely around.
ダンスダンスダンスを踊れ踊れ
Dance, dance, dance, dance away.
マジネガティブくわして シラケさせて
Feeding real negativity, dampening the mood,
一般ピーポーで個性派で個性的で
An ordinary person, individualistic and unique,
定番のネタもはや全部光栄
Even standard jokes are an honor by now.
私がこれまでどれだけ努力したかしてないかにかかわらないまま 独自の物差し当てがってんなよ 今に見てろくそが
Without caring how much effort I've made or not, don't measure me with your own ruler! Just you wait, asshole.
何をやってもうまくいかない 脳内大戦争だもんね 突っ立ってたって
Nothing I do goes right, there's a total war in my brain even while standing around.
愛して 愛して
Love me, love me.
第三者目線は手厚い手当
A third party's perspective offers generous care.
何をやってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right.
先戦は恐々だもんね 突っ立ってたって
The front lines are filled with fear, even while standing around.
愛して 愛さないね
Love me, you won't love me, right?
心配してるフリしてんのも気付いてるよ
I notice you're only pretending to worry about me.
何をやってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right.
何にもやってないだけじゃない？
Isn't it just that you haven't tried anything at all?
U
[Song: U]
ラライラライ 誰も知らない 名もない今を賭けてゆくの あの三日月に手を伸ばして
La-lai-la-lai, betting on this unknown, nameless moment, reaching out to that crescent moon.
ラライラライ 君を知りたい 声にならない 臆病な弱さを たとえ何度崩れようとも
La-lai-la-lai, I want to know you, my wordless, cowardly weakness, no matter how many times I break down...
ラクラクラライ ラライ ラライ ラクラクラライ
La-kura-kura-lai, la-lai, la-lai, la-kura-kura-lai...
ガラスの靴がパチンと切られたそのとき 世界と逸れてしまったみたいだ
When the glass slipper snapped off, it felt as though I'd strayed from the world.
手繰り寄せる景色が悲しく笑うなら 恐れずまぶたを閉じてごらん
If the scenery I pull close laughs sadly, close your eyes without fear and see.
寂しんぼさんこちらへどうぞ 鼓動の鳴るほうへさあ
Lonely one, come over here, toward the sound of beating hearts.
踵を打ち鳴らせどうぞ 心踊るほうへさあ
Tap your heels, toward where your heart dances.
蜃気楼に飛び乗って 逆さまの世界乗りこなして
Leap onto a mirage, master this upside-down world!
ラライラライ 止まない愛を知りたいと願うおまじない 時を超えて朝から夜まで
La-lai-la-lai, a spell wishing to know an endless love, transcending time from morning to night.
ラライラライ 君を知りたい 何一つ見逃さぬように 時は誰も待ってくれないの
La-lai-la-lai, I want to know you, so as not to miss a single thing; time waits for no one.
残酷な運命が 抗えぬ宿命が 考える間もなく押し寄せるなら
If cruel fate and irresistible destiny wash over without time to think,
目に見えなくたって 意地信じてみたいの 恐れずに一歩踏み出したら
even if invisible, I want to believe in my resolve; if I take a step without fear...
鼓動の鳴るほうへさあ 踵を打ち鳴らせどうぞ 心踊るほうへさあ
Toward the sound of beating hearts, tap your heels, toward where your heart dances!
寂しんぼさんこちらへどうぞ 鼓動の鳴るほうへさあ 踵を打ち鳴らせどうぞ 心踊るほうへさあ
Lonely one, come over here, toward the beating heart, tap your heels, toward where your heart dances!
空飛ぶ鯨に飛び乗って 逆さまの世界踊り尽くせ
Jump onto a flying whale, dance through this upside-down world!
ラライラライ 誰も知らない 名もない今を賭けてゆくの あの三日月に手を伸ばして
La-lai-la-lai, betting on this unknown, nameless moment, reaching out to that crescent moon.
ラライラライ 君を知りたい 声にならない 臆病な弱さを たとえ何度崩れようとも
La-lai-la-lai, I want to know you, my wordless, cowardly weakness, no matter how many times I break down...
夢ならば覚めないで 現実なんてさ もう見たくもないから
If this is a dream, don't wake me, because I don't want to see reality anymore.
時は誰も待ってくれないの
Time waits for no one...
はーい、みなさん！
Hi, everyone!
どうですか？楽しんでいただいておりますか？
How is it? Are you all enjoying yourselves?
世界が…
The world...
滅びていってるわ。滅びてますね、どんどん。
...is perishing. It's perishing, bit by bit.
困っちゃいますねー。
That's troubling, isn't it?
さあ、宿敵に勝つために
Now, in order to defeat her arch-enemy,
彼女はなんと！
she has brought...
仲間を連れてくるそうです！
...a companion with her, it seems!
と言ことで、ここからはゲストパートが始まっていくよー！
So with that, the guest part is starting now!
それじゃあみんな、いってらっしゃい！
Alright everyone, off you go!
革命を起こせ 願うは自虐？
Cause a revolution! Is your wish self-deprecation?
拝啓 131937210... マジと？
Dear 131937210... Seriously?
勝つか負けるか
Win or lose,
ドローなんてないわ
there's no such thing as a draw.
幕開けるわ
The curtain rises.
ガチ勢してラッキーマネー どっちも無理
Try-hards, lucky money, both are impossible.
光るか否か 自分次第だ
Whether you shine or not is up to you.
余裕で売り切りたい 部屋届いてやーい
Wanting an easy sell-out, hoping it reaches my room, yay yay.
そこそこか そこそこえす 重なるの私だ
So-so or so-so S, I'm the one who overlaps.
ステイもいい 勝つなら平常心
Staying is fine, if you win, stay calm.
ねぇ プレイボーイギャン？ Don't get in my way
Hey playboy gang? Don't get in my way.
じゃあね 黙って
Bye then, shut up.
1 2 3 1 2 3 1 2 3
シーだ シーだ
Shh, shh.
1 2 3 1 2 3 1 2 3
うんうん 半分フリーキー 待って 嫌 投げるのアンササイ
Mhm mhm half freaky wait no throwing answer sigh.
拘束時間 その小ささ 指示打つから 嫌ですわ
Restricted time, that smallness, giving orders, I hate it.
セイ グッバイや
Say goodbye.
あっちこっちそっち どっち なっち なっちや
Here, there, over there, which way, standard, standard.
見尽くした道より
Rather than the path you've seen through,
ヤムヤムヤ からまりそう
Yum yum yum, seems like it'll get entangled.
でもまだ 止めないで
But don't stop yet.
飲まれそう 声々 それぞれに
About to be swallowed, voices, each to their own.
Get past pain あーあ あんたここまで？
Get past pain, Ah ah, is this all you got?
後ろだけ見て頂戴
Look only behind you, please.
ガチ勢してラッキーマネー どっちも無理
Try-hards, lucky money, both are impossible.
光るか否か 自分次第だ
Whether you shine or not is up to you.
余裕で売り切りたい 部屋届いてやーい
Wanting an easy sell-out, hoping it reaches my room, yay yay.
そこそこか そこそこえす 重なるの私だ
So-so or so-so S, I'm the one who overlaps.
ステイもいい 勝つなら平常心
Staying is fine, if you win, stay calm.
ねぇ プレイボーイギャン？ Don't get in my way
Hey playboy gang? Don't get in my way.
じゃあね 黙って
Bye then, shut up.
1 2 3 1 2 3 1 2 3
シーだ シーだ
Shh, shh.
1 2 3 1 2 3 1 2 3
まさかのバイバイ
An unexpected bye-bye.
1 2 3 1 2 3 1 2 3
シーだ シーだ
Shh, shh.
短い夢を重ねて
Overlapping short dreams,
永遠にしてゆく華の
making flowers eternal...
偽りが切ない
The falsehoods are painful.
閉じ込めた命の
Confined life's...
孤独を君に捧げる
...solitude, I offer to you,
Preserved Roses
体の奥 溢れるものを
That which overflows deep within the body,
孤高と変えているだけ
is merely transformed into solitude.
すべてが消滅を告げるなんて
For everything to announce annihilation...
ゆとりを許させないで
Don't allow room for error.
光と闇の どちらにでもなれる
Able to become either light or darkness,
くじけないで
don't lose heart.
望まぬ朝は もう来ない
The unwanted morning will come no more,
鮮やかさだけを
only vividness...
繰り返し
...repeating...
つながり
...connections...
終わり
...ends...
影はまた
...the shadow again...
短い夢を重ねて
Overlapping short dreams,
永遠にしてゆく華の
making flowers eternal...
偽りが切なく
The falsehoods are painful,
阻む世界を傷つける
scarring the world that obstructs.
願うなら魅せさせる
If you wish, show me.
だから遠く消えないで
So don't disappear into the distance.
君が見る明日の
The new breath...
新しい息吹を
...of tomorrow that you see,
伸ばした腕に向かえる
reach out your arms to welcome it,
離さない
never let go.
無傷のまま溶け出す熱を
The warmth melting away unscarred,
愛を探ぐる思い
thoughts seeking love...
汚れ合ってしまう
Before we end up staining each other,
前に進むと決めた
I decided to move forward.
やがてこぼれ落ち散らばる水に
On the water that eventually spills and scatters,
鮮やかに心を映し出せるなら
if I can vividly reflect my heart,
囚われの歌と引き換えに
in exchange for a captive song...
激しい色注いで
Pouring intense colors,
飾り立てた幻を
an embellished illusion.
君が信じるなら 真実だって超えるだろう
If you believe in it, it will surpass even the truth.
移ろう時を止めて
Stop the shifting time,
崩す術も知らないで
without even knowing how to break it down.
血を流すその手は
Those bloodstained hands
閉じ込めたい命を
hold the life I want to confine.
僕を君に捧げる
I offer myself to you,
求めている
seeking you out.
短夜を重ねて
Accumulating short nights,
永遠にして行く花の
of the flowers that become eternal,
偽りが切なく
the falsehood is painfully bitter,
拒む世界を傷つける
hurting a refusing world.
願うなら咲かせる
If I wish, I'll make it bloom.
だから遠く消えないで
So please don't fade away into the distance.
君が見る未来の
The future you see,
眩しい息吹を
its dazzling breath,
伸ばした腕に迎える
I welcome into my outstretched arms,
離さない
never letting go.
何も知らない 何も知らない
I know nothing, I know nothing.
何も見ていない 誰をも見ていない
I haven't seen anything, I haven't seen anyone.
空を見ても 見えない夜の
Even if I look at the sky, in the unseen night,
欠けた月にウサギ
there's a rabbit on the waning moon.
これはなんだ？ それが何か？
What is this? What about it?
ここは悲しい それでよろしい
It's sad here. That's fine then.
走る 逃げる 逃がす そらす
Running, fleeing, letting go, looking away.
次の欠けた場所へ
Off to the next chipped place.
あらら あらら あらら あらら あらら あらら
Oh dear, oh dear, oh my, oh my...
妄想 留め処なく
Delusions without end,
騒擾 咎めなく
disturbance without blame.
衝動 収まらず
Impulse uncontained,
なぜか なぜか なぜか
why, why, why?
知らん！
I don't know!
最悪だ！ 感情論と服を脱いで踊れ
It's the worst! Strip off emotional logic and clothes and dance!
最底辺か？ なんだかんだ言ったって なんやかんやで
Is this rock bottom? After all is said and done, one way or another,
最悪だ どうもこうもしてよ 勝手に仕上がれ
it's the worst! Do whatever, get yourself together!
最底辺か？ いやーもう本当最悪だ
Is this rock bottom? Man, it's really the worst!
寝ても覚めても付きまとう
Haunting me whether asleep or awake,
見えぬ意識の裏側で
behind unseen consciousness,
大きく開いた黒い穴
a dark hole gaping wide.
わかる わかる わかる
I get it, I get it, I get it.
許す 許せん 許す 許せん
Forgive, unforgivable, forgive, unforgivable.
可愛い えへへ 怖い
Cute, ehehe, scary.
リンゴ ゴリラ
Apple, gorilla,
ラッパ パセリ
trumpet, parsley,
ラクダ ダボラ デモ隊
camel, big talker, demonstration march!
私達 絶対に見てません
We definitely didn't see anything!
言ってもません 聞いてもません 知ったこっちゃありません
Haven't said a word, haven't heard a thing, it's none of our business!
光に一味 影に一匹
One faction in the light, one beast in the shadow,
許されざる思考 当てはまらない異常
unforgivable thoughts, an anomaly that doesn't fit,
正々で生きていこうじゃありませんか
shall we live fair and square?
高度な物持たず
Holding nothing sophisticated,
競争 意味もなく
competition without meaning,
英雄 自己満足
hero, self-satisfaction.
だから だから だから
That's why, that's why, that's why...
最高だ！ 脳が崩壊してんだ ぶっ壊して叫べ！
It's the best! The brain is collapsing, smash it up and scream!
最良か？ なんでなんつって バコバコ弾けちゃって
Is it the best? Saying why and how, bursting wildly!
最高だ！ 狂喜乱舞で結構 勝手に生き延びろ
It's the best! Wild dancing is fine, survive on your own!
最良か？ いやーもう本当最高だ
Is it the best? Man, it really is the best!
昔々の思いつき
An idea from long ago,
もう有息無意味の人だかり
already a crowd of breathing, meaningless people.
無邪気無敵の生まれつき
Innocent and invincible by nature,
それが それが それが
that's, that's, that's...
無責任集合体 あんたもわたしも関係ない
The irresponsibility aggregate! You and I have nothing to do with it!
無責任集合体
An irresponsible collective,
楽しくやってりゃもう万歳
if we're having fun, then hooray!
勝手にやってりゃ問題なし
If we do as we like, no problem.
俺は知らない 何も知らない
I don't know, I know nothing.
何も見てない 誰も見てない
I saw nothing, nobody saw anything.
記憶違い 夢の話
A mistake in memory, a talk of dreams.
そういうことで それじゃ
And with that, goodbye then.
充電器貸して 端末のせいだ
Lend me a charger, it's my device's fault.
電池が減った
The battery died.
終電逃して また私のせいだ
Missed the last train, it's my fault again.
声が増えるの？ なんで？
Why are our voices multiplying?
繋がっていようね
Let's stay connected.
執着心を持ち込んで
Bringing our obsessions along,
お互い足を引っ張り合おう
let me drag each other down.
沈殿した思い出で ずっといっしょ
Forever together in settled memories.
傘を開けて 誰も見つめていない気がしたんだ
Opening my umbrella, I felt like no one was looking.
存在し損ねて 誰の目にも映らないようにしたんだ
Failing to exist, I made sure I was invisible.
そうやって乗っかった 孤独感もめちゃくちゃになった
Even the loneliness I rode on became a mess.
私失った 私だって
I lost myself, even I...
欲しくて仕方ない こんな身体いらない
I want it so bad, I don't need a body like this.
使いたいとも思えない もう
I don't even want to use it anymore.
共に過ごした日々が
If only the days we spent together,
些細な幸せが
and that trivial happiness,
掛け替えのないトラウマになってくれたらいいな
would become an irreplaceable trauma.
離れ離れなんて 誰かがつくった嘘だよね
Being apart must be a lie someone made up.
あなたの一生の後悔として 添い遂げるよ
I'll stay with you as your life's regret.
大切なものって何？
What is something precious?
今無くしたそれ
That thing you just lost.
私と間違いを犯そうよ
Let's make a mistake together.
取り返しがつかないね
There's no turning back now.
健やかなるときも 痛めるときも
In sickness and in health,
愚かさの果てまで ずっといっしょ
to the end of foolishness, forever together.
もうちょっと普通に 悲しいこと悲しいと思いたかった
I wanted to feel sad normally when things were sad.
蝶々の抽出に 感情委託して楽になりたかった
I wanted to ease my mind by offloading my feelings.
精一杯 一生懸命に 生きてくださいね
Please live your life with all your might.
私だって死にたくて仕方ない
I want to die so badly too.
あなたの言いなりになっていたくないの
I don't want to be at your command.
あなただけ一人で 私の目を盗んで
Don't think you can be happy all by yourself,
幸せになろうなんて思わないで
stealing away behind my back.
髪を乾かしてくれた夜から
Ever since the night you dried my hair,
私壊されたのよ
I was broken, you know.
あなたの一生の後悔として 添い遂げるよ
I'll stay with you as your life's regret.
外れなくなってしまった 指輪みたいに
Like a ring that can no longer be taken off.
何度もずっと フラッシュバックしている 最低だよ
It keeps flashing back over and over, it's terrible.
一緒にいたときのほうが 私可愛かったのに
Even though I was cuter when we were together.
あなたの一生の後悔として 添い遂げるよ
I'll stay with you as your life's regret.
大切なものって何？
What is something precious?
今無くしたそれ
That thing you just lost.
私と間違いを犯そうよ
Let's make a mistake together.
取り返しがつかないね
There's no turning back, is there?
健やかなるときも 痛めるときも
In sickness and in health,
他の誰かが咎めてくれても
even if someone else tries to stop us,
お揃いの地獄で ずっといっしょ
forever together in our matching hell.
刃渡り数センチの不信感が
A blade of mistrust a few centimeters wide,
挙句の果て頸脈を刺し込んじゃって
ended up stabbing into my jugular vein.
病細な愛が飛び出すもんで
As a sickly love came gushing out,
レスポール抱いてはナイフで割いた
I clutched my Les Paul and slashed it with a knife.
数学と理科が好きでした
I liked math and science,
国語がどうもダメで嫌いでした
but I was hopeless at Japanese and hated it.
正しいのがどれか考えたら
When I pondered which one was correct,
どれも正解というオチでした
the punchline was that all of them were right.
本日の宿題は 無個性の僕のこと
Today's homework is about my personality-less self.
不自由ない 生きていきたくて
Wanting to live without restrictions,
でもどうして 僕たちは
but why are we...
時々に いや毎日
sometimes, no, every day,
悲しいって言った
saying we're sad,
寂しいって言った
saying we're lonely?
黒板のこの漢字が読めますか
Can you read these kanji on the blackboard?
あの子の心象は読めますか
Can you read that child's state of mind?
その心を黒く染めたのは
The one who dyed that heart black...
おい誰なんだよ
Hey, who was it?
そろばんでこの式が解けますか
Can you solve this equation on an abacus?
あの子の首の輪も解けますか
Can you loosen the noose around that child's neck?
僕たちこのままでいいんですか
Is it okay for us to stay like this?
おいどうすんだよ
Hey, what are we going to do?
もうどうだっていいや
Ah, whatever, I don't care anymore.
今までだって 僕たちは
Even until now, we...
存在の証明によって生きていて
have lived by proving our existence.
どうしようもないくらいの強情を
A stubbornness that can't be helped,
ずっと
all this time...
抱え込んでいたんだ
we've been holding onto it.
昨日の宿題は
Yesterday's homework,
相変わらず解けないや
as expected, I still can't solve it.
過不足ない 不自由ない
Neither lacking nor overflowing, without restriction,
生きていきたくて
wanting to live...
でもどうして
But why...
僕たちの胸元の固まりは
does the lump in our chests say,
消えたいって言うんだ
"I want to disappear"?
死にたいって言うんだ
Why does it say, "I want to die"?
黒板のこの漢字が読めますか
Can you read these kanji on the blackboard?
あの子の心象は読めますか
Can you read that child's state of mind?
その心を黒く染めたのは
The one who dyed that heart black...
おい誰なんだよ
Hey, who was it?
そろばんでこの式が解けますか
Can you solve this equation on an abacus?
あの子の首の輪も解けますか
Can you loosen the noose around that child's neck?
僕たちこのままでいいんですか
Is it okay for us to stay like this?
おいどうすんだよ
Hey, what are we going to do?
面積比の公式言えますか
Can you state the formula for area ratio?
子供の時の夢は言えますか
Can you tell me your childhood dream?
その夢すら溝に捨てたのは
The one who threw even that dream into the gutter...
おい誰なんだよ
Hey, who was it?
もう知ってんだろ
You already know, don't you?
いつになりゃ大人になれますか
When will I finally become an adult?
そもそも大人とは一体全体何ですか
What even is an "adult" in the first place?
どなたに伺えばいいんですか
Who am I supposed to ask?
おいどうすんだよ
Hey, what am I supposed to do?
もうどうだっていいや
Ah, whatever, I don't care anymore.
はい！
Yeah!
はーい、皆さん！
Hello, everyone!
どうも！ということで
Hello! So then...
皆さん見てください！
Everyone, look at this!
メガホンマイク！
A megaphone mic!
そしてたくさんのゲストが来てくれました！
And so many guests came to join today!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
カッコいいでしょ？
It's cool, right?
どうですか？
What do you think?
カッコいいよね！
It's super cool, isn't it?
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
それでは皆さん！
Now then, everyone!
多分ドキドキ心待ちにしていたでしょう！
You've probably been anxiously waiting for this!
重大告知その1が...
Major Announcement Part 1...
VTRございますので
is in a video clip,
一旦そちらを見ていただこうと思います！
so I'd like you to check that out first!
それでは、どうぞー！
Here it goes!
天音かなた 2nd Album
Amane Kanata 2nd Album
Trigger
2025.07.23 ON SALE
Keep your finger on the "Trigger".
みんなー！アルバム出るぞー！
Everyone! An album is coming out!
Vどうでしたかー？
How was the video?
ということでね、本当に...
So yeah, really...
詳細はまた後でという感じで...
Details will come later...
ありがとうございます！皆さんの...
Thank you so much! Thanks to...
おかげでまたアルバムを出すことができます！
everyone, I'm able to release another album!
そしてその後にね、もっとすごい告知もあるので絶対最後まで見てください！
And after that, there's an even bigger announcement, so make sure to watch until the end!
それではね...
Now then...
そちらのアルバムの中から1曲新曲を聞いてもらいます！
I'll have you listen to a new song from that album!
それでは聞いてください！
Please take a listen!
きゅーびっと。
Cupid.
何気ない声が
An offhand voice...
ちょっと妄想まがいな
somewhat like a delusion.
いつからかそれが
At some point, that...
くだーるー ほしくなる
Falling down... wanting you...
Ah
気づいてんじゃない？
Haven't you noticed?
きっと甘い
It's surely sweet,
そんな言葉で yeah
with words like that, yeah.
もう羽はまっちゃって
My wings are already hooked,
ねえ酔っちゃって
hey, I'm intoxicated,
ねえ矢を撃っちゃって
hey, shoot your arrow!
きゅーぴっと！
Cupid!
今落ちてく飛んでく何？
Falling now, flying now—what is this?
うわっつく心はわん・つー
My restless heart goes one, two!
うまく恋熱感して
Skillfully sensing the heat of love...
もうキミは想定外
You're completely beyond my expectations!
かなわなーいな
I just can't compete with you.
キミのきゅーぴっとです
I'm your Cupid!
無我夢中中
Completely head over heels!
きっと夢に出てくる
I'll surely appear in your dreams!
ちゅっちゅっちゅ
Chu, chu, chu!
痛いのよ今も
It hurts even now,
救急です
it's an emergency!
また夢遊遊
Sleepwalking once again...
ちょっと涙出てくる
A few tears start to fall...
きゅっきゅっきゅ
Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze!
ぎゅっと抱きしめて！
Hold me tight!
どうして？
Why?
らったったー らったったー
Rat-tat-ta, rat-tat-ta!
キミはまだ知らない事情
Circumstances you don't know about yet,
あたしも見えてないでしょ
you can't see the real me either, right?
なっちゃったー なっちゃったー
It happened, it happened!
あの子には見せちゃう微笑
Showing that smile to that girl,
想うだけで熱 上昇
just thinking about it makes my temperature rise!
あぁ油断しちゃう その眼差し
Ah, I let my guard down under that gaze of yours.
探しつづけた 宝石みたい
Like a gemstone I've been searching for...
でもまだ まだ
But still, not yet...
びびっつく心はピンチだ
My electric heart is in a pinch!
羽化する私を愛して
Love me as I emerge from my cocoon!
焦げつく苦味もあーして
Do that to the scorching bitterness too...
もうあたし最底辺
I've hit rock bottom now,
やめられないから
because I can't stop!
キミのきゅーぴっとです
I'm your Cupid!
また夢中中
Infatuated all over again!
もっと欲しくなってく
I want you more and more!
ちゅっちゅっちゅ
Chu, chu, chu!
期待をしちゃうよ
I'm getting my hopes up!
Give you らぶ
Give you love!
感情浮遊遊
My feelings are floating away...
ずっと気持ちあふれる
My emotions keep overflowing!
きゅっきゅっきゅ
Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze!
ぎゅっと抱きしめて！
Hold me tight!
もう隠せないけど
I can't hide it anymore,
止まらない鼓動
my heart beating uncontrollably...
夢から覚めて
Wake up from the dream...
気づいて、いま
Notice me right now!
2025.8.13 天音かなた 1stソロライブ 開催決定
[2025.8.13 Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live Announced!]
Stay Tuned...
ルールールールー...
Ru ru ru ru...
君の中にある 赤と青き線
The red and blue lines inside of you...
それらが結ばれるのは 心の臓
Where they meet is inside the heart.
風の中でも負けないような声で
With a voice that won't lose to the wind,
届ける言葉を今は育ててる
I am nurturing words to deliver to you.
時はまくらぎ
Time is a sleeper,
風はにきはだ
wind is smooth skin,
星はうぶすな
stars are the guardian deity,
人はかげろう
humans are a shimmering haze.
なんで泣いてるのと聞かれ答えれる
When asked why I'm crying, I can answer...
涙なんかじゃ 僕ら出会えたことの意味にはまるで追いつかない
But tears could never capture the full meaning of our meeting.
この身ひとつじゃ
With just this body of mine,
じゃ足りない叫び
my cries are not enough.
君の手触れたときにだけ震えた
My heart shook only when I touched your hand...
心があったよ
I realized I had a heart.
意味をいくつ越えれば僕らは辿り
How many meanings must we cross over...
つけるのかな
before we can finally reach our destination?
愚かさでいい
Foolishness is fine.
醜さでいい
Ugliness is fine.
正しさのその先で
Beyond righteousness,
君と手を取りたい
I want to hold hands with you.
思い出せない
Unrecallable...
大切な記憶
precious memories.
言葉にならない
Words cannot express...
ここにある思い
the feelings residing right here.
もしかしたら
Just maybe...
just maybe...
空だけでこの心は出来てる
my heart is made of nothing but the sky.
もしかしたら
Just maybe...
just maybe...
君に気づいてと今もその胸を
asking you to notice, even now inside that chest...
打ち鳴らす
it continues to beat.
なんで泣いてるのと聞かれ答えれる
When asked why I'm crying, I can answer.
涙なんかじゃ僕が出逢えたことの意味にはまるで
Tears alone could never begin to match...
追いつかない
the meaning of us meeting.
この身ひとつじゃ
With just this body of mine,
じゃ足りない叫び
my cries are not enough.
君の手触れたときにだけ震えた
My heart shook only when I touched your hand...
心があったよ
I realized I had a heart.
意味をいくつ越えれば僕らは辿り
How many meanings must we cross over...
つけるのかな
before we can finally reach our destination?
愚かさでいい
Foolishness is fine.
醜さでいい
Ugliness is fine.
正しさのその先で
Beyond righteousness,
君と生きてきたい
I want to go on living with you.
皆さん、天音かなた2025年生誕ライブ見てくださってありがとうございました！
Everyone, thank you so much for watching Amane Kanata's 2025 Birthday Live!
たくさんね、重大告知が発表されて、わけが分からなくなっていると思うので、少しまとめて紹介します！
With so many major announcements, I'm sure it's overwhelming, so let me summarize them for you!
ということで1つ目！天音かなた2ndアルバム『Trigger』の発売が2025年7月23日水曜日に決定しました！
First up, Amane Kanata's 2nd album "Trigger" will be released on Wednesday, July 23, 2025!
こちらはですね、完全新作全9曲入っております。
This album features 9 all-new tracks.
そして完全生産限定盤、通常盤A、Bの3形態で発売となります！
It will be released in three versions: Limited Edition, Standard Edition A, and Standard Edition B!
そしてですね、なんとまた全国流通ということで、日本中のCDショップで購入できますよ！
And once again, it's a nationwide release, so you can buy it at CD shops across Japan!
まずはですね、完全生産限定盤の詳細はこちらでございます。
First, here are the details for the Limited Edition.
さーしるさんにイラストをご担当いただきました。
The illustration was done by Sashiru-san.
限定A4サイズボックスの超豪華パッケージの中に、『Trigger』アクリルスタンド、PRカード「天音かなた」、秘密の特訓ノート、CDが入っております。
Inside the deluxe A4-sized limited box, it includes a "Trigger" acrylic stand, PR card "Amane Kanata", secret training notebook, and CD.
アクスタはアルバム3種すべてのイラストを使用したミニアクスタ！
The acrylic stand is a mini stand using illustrations from all three album editions!
プロカデザインは通常盤Aデザインのおしおしおママのイラストを使った限定デザイン！
The PR card features a limited design using Oshioshio-mama's illustration from Standard Edition A!
そして秘密の特訓ノートには、僕が実際のレコーディングで使ったメモ入りの歌詞の資料や、アルバムの制作日記、みんなへの手紙も入っております！
And the secret training notebook includes my handwritten recording lyrics, production diary, and a letter to everyone!
そして通常盤はこちらの2種。
And here are the two Standard Editions.
通常盤Aは我らがおしおしお先生ママのイラスト！
Standard Edition A features an illustration by our mama, Oshioshio-sensei!
そして通常盤Bは前回のアルバムに引き続き平山寛菜先生にお願いいたしました！
And for Standard Edition B, as with the previous album, it was illustrated by Kanna Hirayama-sensei!
どちらも特典透明三方背スリーブに入っております！
Both come packaged in a special clear 3-sided sleeve!
そしてですね、今回も通常盤A、Bにはランダムアナザージャケット全6種類のうち1枚が付いてきます！
And once again, Standard Editions A and B come with 1 random bonus jacket out of 6 designs!
そしてそして！数量限定で僕の直筆サインが入っているかも！？ということでぜひ手に入れてください！
Plus, a limited number might even contain my handwritten signature, so be sure to get yours!
そして各店舗の購入特典ももちろん大充実していますので、みんなどれにするかじっくり決めてください。
Each store's purchase bonus is super packed as well, so take your time deciding which one to get.
本日このあと配信が終わり次第、予約開始です！
Pre-orders start right after today's stream ends!
そして1点、ホロライブオフィシャルショップのアルバム購入についての注意事項です。
One important note regarding album purchases on the Hololive Official Shop:
完全生産限定盤は発売日のお届けとなりますので、
The Limited Edition will be delivered on the release date,
2ndアルバム通常盤以外のグッズなどの商品は同時購入はできません。
so it cannot be purchased together with goods other than the 2nd Album Standard Edition.
通常盤は他のグッズとの同時購入が可能ですが、店頭発売日以降のお届けになる可能性があるのでご注意ください。
Standard Editions can be bought with other goods, but note that delivery may be after the retail release date.
詳しくは販売サイトの注意事項をご確認ください。
Please check the sales site's notes for full details.
ということでこれ、ややこしすぎるので明日配信で...
So yeah, this is pretty complex, so tomorrow on stream...
詳しく説明いたします。
I will explain in detail.
そしてもう一つの重大告知！天音かなた、
And another major announcement! Amane Kanata...
2025年8月13日に1stソロライブの開催が決定しましたー！
...has decided to hold her 1st Solo Live on August 13th, 2025!
やっと来たー！ということでですね、
It's finally here! So then,
ライブ会場やチケット、グッズなどの詳しい情報はまた改めて発表しますので、
detailed info on the live venue, tickets, merch, etc., will be announced later,
お前ら、とりあえず8月13日水曜日をあけておいてください！
so you guys, for now, please keep Wednesday, August 13th open!
それから3つ目、本日解禁いたしました新曲「きゅぴっど。」はTeddyLoidさんに制作いただいております！
And third, the new song "Kyupid." released today was produced by TeddyLoid-san!
2ndアルバムにももちろん入ります！
It will of course be included in the 2nd album!
そしてこのあとMV公開して、24時から配信リリースもいたしますのでぜひチェックしてください！
And after this, the MV will be released, and digital release starts at 24:00, so please check it out!
ライブとアルバムはハッシュタグ #撃ち抜けかなた と言うものがありますので感想どしどしお待ちしております！
We have the hashtag #撃ち抜けかなた for the live and album, so send us all your thoughts!
アルバム配信が終わり次第、受付、予約受付開始なのでぜひチェックしてください！
Pre-orders will open as soon as the stream ends, so please check it out!
そして4つ目！天音かなた誕生日記念2025のグッズ出ますー！
And fourth! Amane Kanata Birthday Celebration 2025 merch is coming out!
誕生日記念フルセット、こんな感じになっておりまして、1つずつ紹介したいと思います。
The Birthday Celebration Full Set looks like this, so let me introduce each item one by one.
まずはアクリルスタンド。これ、みんなとお忍びデート中で、グッズでパ―カー出る、それとお揃いのやつ着てるから、
First, the acrylic stand! It's an in-disguise date with everyone, wearing a matching hoodie to the merch,
みんなグッズ買ってくれたらこれでお揃いになります！そのパーカーはこの次！
so if you buy the merch, we'll match! That hoodie is up next!
こちら！かなパーカー！かなたその雰囲気も入って、すごくおしゃれな感じで、イラストも背中にめっちゃデカくついています！
Here! Kana-hoodie! It has Kanataso's vibe, super stylish, and has a huge illustration on the back!
みんなとお揃いになるからぜひよろしくお願いします！
It will match with everyone, so please get one!
みんなじゃなくてかなたそとお揃いね！
I mean, it'll match with Kanataso!
で、3つ目は推し活がはかどるポーチ！これ、小さいぬいぐるみとかキーホルダーとか入れられるクリアポケットに缶バッジも入れられるし、リュックとかにも引っ掛けられるからカスタマイズしてね！
Third is the Oshi-katsu Handy Pouch! Put plushies or keychains in the clear pocket, add badges, and hook it to your bag to customize!
そして次は「かなたそ推しだよね？バッジ」！
Next is the "You're a Kanataso Fan, Right? Badge"!
こちら、僕推しの平民のためのバッジ！かなたそ推しね。
This badge is for the heimin who support me! Kanataso fans.
えーっと、かなたそちゃんとウパの両方ついています。この文字のところとかなたそちゃんとウパのところはなんか、
Um, it features both Kanataso-chan and Upah. The text, Kanataso-chan, and Upah are...
半立体らしい！すっごい可愛いぜ！
...apparently semi-3D! Super cute!
そして、ポストカードがフルセット購入特典でついてきます。
And a postcard comes as a full set purchase bonus.
ここには直筆サインが入りますが、この直筆サインはね、今回ね、全員に書かせていただきますので、タイヨロでございます！
It features a handwritten signature, and this time I will sign every single one, so thanks in advance!
そして、ホロカPRカードもついてくるよ！
And a Holoca PR card is included too!
タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、2024年9月から発売されたホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚つきます。
As a full set bonus for talent premium merch, you get 1 card usable in the Hololive Official Card Game launched in Sept 2024.
同梱するカードは、ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入されたお客様のみ対象となります。
The bundled card is only available for purchases made on the Hololive Production Official Shop.
特典につくのはゲームで1枚だけ使用でき、推しをアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンカードです。
The bonus card is an Oshi Holomen Card, a key card you can include 1 copy of to showcase your favorite member.
カードの詳細や遊び方については、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームの公式ホームページにてご確認ください。
For card details and how to play, please check the official Hololive Official Card Game website.
同梱するカードは日本語版のみとなりますのでご了承ください。
Please note that the included card is available in Japanese only.
ということでね！さすがのかなたそもう口が回らなくなってきていますが、
So with that! As expected, even Kanataso is getting tongue-tied,
皆さんついてこられていましたでしょうか？
were you all able to keep up?
ぜひぜひね、たくさん重大告知ありましたが、いろいろ整理して、皆さん、あのぜひ全てチェックしてもらえたら嬉しいなと思います！
We had lots of big announcements, so after digesting them, I'd love it if you checked everything out!
それではまた明日お会いしましょう！バイバーイ！
Well then, see you again tomorrow! Bye-bye!
俺もお前も夢の跡
Both you and I are traces of a dream
失うものが何処にある
Where is anything left to lose?
薄汚い俺はブタ
Filthy pig that I am
ハイエナ共がしゃぶる
The hyenas suck me dry
手にしたもの 嘘と肉
What I gained: lies and meat
涙まみれの体 食らいえ
Devour this tear-stained body
AH-WOO AH-WOO
あんたの眼が俺を犯す
Your eyes violate me
俺は弾ける TRIGGER
I am a TRIGGER ready to burst
侮蔑と唾 吐きかけて
Spitting contempt and saliva
脳天 突っ散らかして行く欲望
Desire piercing straight through the skull
血が俺の友 奴はこう言う
Blood is my friend, and it says:
『もがき足掻け
"Struggle and squirm,
死ぬまで這いつくばれ』
crawl on your knees until you die"
AH-WOO AH-WOO
俺もお前も夢の跡
Both you and I are traces of a dream
失うものが何処にある
Where is anything left to lose?